yeah sure you're looking at the numbers
i think on the uh general insurance
right aside right the monthly numbers
how are they uh that's correct the
october general insurance numbers were
released and it's disappointment for one
player and you know the numbers have
been strong for another player so for
icici lombard the numbers have been
slightly disappointing in the month of
october the october premium is down
about 12 percent uh when compared on a
year-on-year basis though they are up 17
when compared to an average of the h1 f5
22 numbers new india assurance strong
performance in the month of october the
premium has grown by about 35 that uh
would be encouraging as far as the
premium collection is concerned uh
though the october premium numbers are
down about four percent when compared to
uh h1 f5 22 so i'm going with the red
for icsl lombard and green for new india
shorts
okay well let's go across to nigel he
has some more numbers that he's tracking
for us nigel what are you looking at
well let's start off with hg those
numbers look quite good and the margins
are the best that we've seen in the last
couple of years so margins did come at
around 27 so going with green on that
one hindustan copper well optically the
numbers look good but a closer look at
it told you that margins have contracted
both on a year and year as well as on a
sequential basis and keep in mind uh you
know you had copper prices that were
rather firm and this is the only company
that's a direct play out there so the
fear is that margins will will only
slide from year on but even assuming
that the second half of the year is much
better than the first half of the year
you come to an eps of around two and a
half rupees that would mean that the
stock is trading at more than 50 times
uh you know on a forward running basis
so going with a bit of a disappointment
out there maybe a tinge of red next up
you have credit access grameen well out
there the numbers looked a little bit
disappointing because the asset quality
did worsen a little bit the gross npas
did wide in on a on a quarter on quarter
basis the restructured book well they
reported closer 180 crores that compares
with nothing in the first quarter of
this year and the calculated provision
coverage ratio well that as well that
contracted on 77 from around three
percent so that looked a little bit
disappointing and finally misha nadu
well um uh the numbers look pretty good
on the top line there was some growth
though there was some bit of margin
compression there was some growth on the
profitability front uh so going with
green out there back to you
okay nigel thank you very much for that
more results uh agam is here to explain
those
sure i start with a couple of names from
the healthcare space we have astrozeneca
pharma it's been a week quarter where
revenues have declined six percent and
margins have come up considerably at
just about 9.1 percent against 17.1
percent year-on-year moving on to png
health and hygiene once again a subdued
quarter with revenues rising just three
percent year-on-year and also 100 basis
points contraction in its ebitda margins
reddington however has had a good
quarter with revenues rising 11 but we
are looking at a 47
growth in ebitda coming in at around 457
crores and finally we have gold rich
agrovet revenues rising nearly 25
percent there has been a little bit of
contraction in margins coming in around
9.1 percent against 10.5 percent and
profit consequently has declined three
percent year on year all right uh let's
go across to sonal now to talk about
some more stocks that are in the news
sonal over to you
thanks a lot for that let me start with
shkelker the stock was logged in upper
circuit yesterday there was a block deal
and now we know the details blackstone
has sold their existing 10 and a half
percent stake in the company at a price
of 173 rupees per share 1.4 crore shares
were traded now who has bought the steak
well it is bought by another fragrance
and flavor company which is called
furmanic aromatics production which is
actually a multinational company it is a
swiss brand and this is the one that has
bought the 10 stake that blackstone sold
so that stock remains in focus z media
has received proposal from a promoter
group entity for further investment in
the company and that's why they have a
board meet on november 12th to consider
proposal to issue shares to the promoter
group entity dixon technologies company
has signed a jv with beetle for
manufacturing telecom and networking
products and this jv has an annual
revenue potential of 1400 to 1600 crore
rupees phenotx chemicals has commenced
production at uh additional ambernath
unit with a plant capacity of 36 000
metric tons and lastly vodafone idea
will be in focus because there is this
et report which suggests that the
company is in talks with banks for loan
recast and if the loan recast is
actually approved it could ease the
financial strain on the telcos that has
a funded exposure of nearly 14 000 crore
rupees however we have not independently
verified this report okay let's see if
vodafone idea can offer something to the
exchanges by of clarification on that
thanks sonal for the list here's a quick
recap it's a long list today stocks that
have positive news flow around them
eminem power grid bhl bosch max
financial igl petronet lng interglobe
aviation spice jet new india assurance
atg mishra dhatu nigam sh kalkar z
media not entertainment z media is the
stock we're looking at vodafone idea
dixon tech stocks that have negative
news around them are icic icici lombard
hindus on copper credit access grameen
astrazeneca and png health and hygiene
so that's our stock list for this
wednesday morning but we're not done yet
the other major major cue is coming from
the commodity markets manisha good
morning oil back to 85.
oh well here it is and it's trading at a
two week highs right now so everywhere
that you look in sense of data and
statements it's all on the positive side
you have seen uh you know higher than
expected china exports that tells you
that the global mood is improving and
saudi aramco says that the global oil
spare capacity is on a decline and
markets should prepare for a tight
market in 2022. jp morgan says that the
global oil demand for the month of
november already is at 100 million
barrels per day so we are looking at
strong demand here uh the return of
global travel strong demand prospects
all of that has been supportive but
today it's all going to be about the
inflation data we already are reacting
to the chinese numbers which are at a
25-month high and the u.s inflation data
in the evening is what the markets are
awaiting right now and ahead of that we
also have seen gains come back in case
of metals gold is trading at a two-month
highs as well so a strong start to
commodities
okay all right uh thanks a lot for that
strong start to commodities let's take a
quick break on that note but so much to
talk about on the other side prakash
dhivan will join in for some stock talk
also blackstone has sold 10.5 stake in
shkaylkar kedar vasay the group ceo of
shkelkar will be joining us on the other
side we also have p radha krishna the
whole time director and ceo of ksuram
industries joining in to discuss their
q2 earnings stay tuned
[Music]
you